Register to The E.Y. Harburg Collection
Yale University Music Library
- Harburgiana, 1929-1968; Series II
  - Correspondence
    - General Correspondence
      - Berman, Abraham, 1961 Jun 6; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - to [Belafonte], Harry, 1963 Dec 10; carbon (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Belafonte, Harry, 1964 Jan 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Berlin, Irving, 1968 May 10; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Botkin, Ben A. (Chief, Archive of American Folk Song, Library of Congress), 1945 Jan 29; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Botkin, Ben A., 1945 Mar 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Botkin, Ben A., 1947 Mar 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Brown, Sandford (Senior Editor, The Saturday Evening Post), 1966 Aug 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - Brown, Sandford, 1966 Oct 26; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
      - to Buchwald, Art, 1963 Jan 11; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 174)
        (Enclosure: "The Pare with Class"-essay)
      - Casey, Joseph E., 1961 Nov 8; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - Chaplin, Saul (Box 22, Folder 175)
        [See Box 21, Folder 172]
      - Corrigan, Mrs. Louis (Rose), [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - to Corrigan, Louis, [1962?]; autograph letter signed, draft (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - Cort, Joe, 1964 Jul 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - Cort, Joe, 1964 Aug 7; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - Corwin, Norman, 1945 Apr 20; telegram (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - Corwin, Norman, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - Crouse, Russel, 1941 Apr 23; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 175)
      - to Dana, Bess, 1962 Feb 28; typed letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Davis, Bradley Otis (Brigadier General, U.S. Army), 1944 Apr 28; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - De Filippo, Eduardo to Wood, Audrey, 1954 Aug 10; typed letter (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - De Vore, Jesse, 1968 Apr 17; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - [Dilworth, Hubert?] Bill, 1963 Oct 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - [Divlin, Jim], 1948 May 8; typed letter (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Divlin, Jim, 1948 Jun 14; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dreyfus, Max, 1958 Jul 19; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Duddy, Lyn, 1968 Jun 10; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Duke, Vernon, 1936 Nov 28; telegram (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dunham, Professor Barrows, 1948 Oct 16; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - to Dunham, Professor Barrows, 1948 Oct 23; carbon (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dunham, Professor Barrows, 1951 Apr 19; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dunham, Professor Barrows, 1954 Oct 12; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dunham, Professor Barrows, 1958 Jun 7; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dunham, Professor Barrows, 1962 Aug 7; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dunham, Professor Barrows, 1965 Feb 1; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Dunham, Professor Barrows, [1965?]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 176)
      - Eastman, Lee (re: Arlen's painting), 1961 Dec 21; telegram (Box 22, Folder 177)
      - Eastman, Lee to Miller, Mitch, 1961 Dec 27; carbon (Box 22, Folder 177)
      - Eastman, Lee to Canady, John, 1961 Dec 28; carbon (Box 22, Folder 177)
        (Enclosure: "Hindsight Forward," mock-commentary by E.Y. Harburg on Arlen's abstract painting)
      - Emery, T. Peck, [no date]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 177)
      - Epstein, Edward, 1968 Jun 12; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 177)
      - to Epstein, Edward, [1968]; autograph letter signed, draft (Box 22, Folder 177)
        (on verso of Epstein, letter)
      - to Epstein, Edward, 1968 Jul 2; carbon (Box 22, Folder 177)
      - Epstein, Edward, 1968 Sep 9; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 177)
      - Essex, Maurice, 1957 Nov 19; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 177)
      - Feinberg, Harold, 1951 Jun 18; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - Feinberg, Marge, [?] Nov 12; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - Fields, Dorothy, [no date]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - Fineshriber Jr., William H., 1945 May 21; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - to Fineshriber Jr., William H., 1945 May 29; carbon (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - Fitelson, Bill, 1968 Jan 26; telegram (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - to Foreman, Carl, 1951 Oct 30; typed letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - Fosse, Bob, [?] Jun 3; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - Friendly, Fred W., 1968 Jun; invitation, signed (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - to Friendly, Fred W., 1968 Jun; authograph letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 178)
      - Gailmor, William S., [?] Aug 21; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Gardner, Gerald C., 1961 Apr 25; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - to Garland, Judy, 1961 Apr 25; carbon, signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Gollobin, Esther [Mrs. Ira], [?] Jun 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Gomberg, Cy, 1952 Oct 31; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Gould, Danny, 1962 Mar 8; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Gould, Danny, 1962 Apr 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Gould, Danny, 1962 Apr 13; carbon (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Green, Johnny, 1958 May 12; carbon (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Grey, Gilliam, [1953?]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Grey, Gilliam, 1953 Oct 6; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Griffith, Beatrice W., 1948 Nov 22; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - to Griffith, Beatrice W., 1948 Dec 1; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - to Griffith, Beatrice W., 1952 Dec 8; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Griffith, Robert E., 1958 Jun 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 179)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1935 Jan 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1935 Feb 11; telegram (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1935 Mar 29; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1935 Jul 3; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1935 Jul 8; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1936 Jun 12; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1938 Mar 25; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1938 Oct 16; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1940 Feb 20; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1940 Dec 23; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1950 Feb 14; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1961 Dec 6; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Gershwin, Ira, 1962 Jan 23; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 180)
      - Hammerstein II, Oscar, 1945 Dec 4; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Hammerstein II, Oscar, 1958 Mar 25; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Hammerstein, Dorothy (Mrs. Oscar), 1958 Jul 30; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Hammerstein, Dorothy, 1959 Nov 23; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Handel, Harry, 1952 Jan 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
        (Enclosure: program for "Hi Ho Broomsticks" by Handel)
      - to Handel, Harry, 1952 Feb 26; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - [Harburg, Ernest?] Ernie, 1965 Jan 3; typed letter (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - [Harburg, Ernest?] Ernie, 1967 Sep 9; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Harris, Leo, 1962 Jul 31; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Hart, Moss, 1959 Nov 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - to Hart, Moss, [1959?]; authograph letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Hauptman, Sally, 1961 Sep 22; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Heilweil, David, 1952 Feb 28; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Hewes, Henry (Drama Critic, Saturday Review), 1961 Oct 13; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Hewes, Henry, 1961 Nov 7; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Holabird, John, 1951 Nov 8; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Homes, Charlie, 1961 Jun 20; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Huberman, Prof. Edward (Department of English, Rutgers), 1961 May 14; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - Huberman, Prof. Edward, [1961?] May 25; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - [Hubley], Faith, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 181)
      - to Jackson, [Mahalia?], 1963 Dec 10; carbon (Box 22, Folder 182)
      - James, Dan (author of Winter Soldiers), 1955 Feb 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 182)
      - to James, Dan, 1955 Apr 7; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 182)
      - Johnson, Hall, 1941 Apr 1; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 182)
      - Jones, Dr. Laurence, 1947 Apr 2; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 182)
      - Joseph, Edmund, 1943 Jun 23; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 182)
      - Kapp, David, [no date]; autograph letter signed, draft (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kasha, Lawrence, 1968 Apr 15; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kasper, Harry, 1962 Apr 27; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, George S., 1943 May 17; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, George S., [1943?]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - to Kaufman, George S., 1943 Jul 27; carbon (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, George S., [1943?]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kay, Hershy, [1953?] Jan 29; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - to Kay, Hershy, 1953 Feb 12; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kazan, Elia, 1944 Dec 26; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Keller, David M., 1967 Dec 6; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kemp, Ed, 1968 Jul 26; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - to Kemp, Ed, 1968 Aug 5; typed letter signed, draft (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kleinerman, Isaac (Producer, CBS News), 1963 Oct 17; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kornheiser, Sidney, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kraft, H. S., 1940 Apr 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - to Kraft, H. S. ("Hychick"), 1940 May 1; carbon (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kraft, H. S., 1943 Feb 17; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - to Kraft, H. S., 1943 Feb 19; carbon (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kroll, Lucy, 1948 Mar 23; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - to Kroll, Lucy, 1948 Mar 24; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kutner, Nanette, 1961 Jun 19; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1934 Oct 31; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1935 Jun 11; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1935 Jun 18; telegram (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1935 Jun 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1935 Jul 8; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1936 Oct 10; telegram (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, [1936-1937?]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1942 Feb 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1942 Feb 9; carbon (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Kaufman, Harry, 1941 Apr 9; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 183)
      - Lahr, Mildred, [1968?]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - to Lahr, Bert, 1941 Mar 4; carbon (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lahr, Bert, 1941 Mar 8; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lahr, John, 1965 Nov 6; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lahr, John, 1967 May 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lamont, Corliss, 1964 Apr 4; typed letter signed, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lance, Saul J., 1962 Dec 4; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Langley, Noel to Randall, Dick, 1968 Mar 1; typed letter signed, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Langley, Noel, 1968 Aug 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Laurents, Arthur, 1963 Jun 4; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Laurents, Arthur, 1963 Jun 6; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lazar, Irving Paul, 1955 Dec 29; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lazar, Irving Paul, 1957 Feb 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Leonard, Dave, 1961 Jun 19; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Levene, Carol, 1953 Feb 3; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lewis, Shari, [196?]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lieberson, Goddard, 1961 Jun 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lieberson, Goddard, 1964 Sep 9; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
        (Enclosure: holograph poem written in Lieberson's honor by E.Y. Harburg)
      - Liebling, Bill [William], 1944 Dec 22; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Liebling, Bill, 1961 Jul 25; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Liebman, Daniel, 1964 Mar 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Liebman, Daniel, 1964 Mar 10; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - L[ifton?], Harold A. (Visual Education Association), 1945 Jun 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - L[ifton?], Harold A., 1945 Oct 18; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lindsay, Dorothy [Mrs. Howard], 1968 Apr 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lippman, Richard W., M.D., 1959 Apr 27; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Littlewood, Joan, 1961 May 25; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - to Littlewood, Joan, 1961 Jun 1; typed letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Littlewood, Joan, 1965 Jan 4; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Logan, Elia, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Logan, Elia, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - [?], Lois, 1936 Nov 29; telegram (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lomax, Alan, [1949?]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - to Lomax, Alan, 1949 Apr 1; carbon (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - to Lopez, Rafael, 1960 Mar 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lyons, Warren, 1963 Feb 25; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - to Lane, Burton, 1953 Apr 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - to Lane, Burton, 1953 Apr 9; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lane, Burton, 1956 Mar 1; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - Lane, Burton, 1961 Jul 12; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 184)
      - to McCulloch, Sam, 1947 Apr 22; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Magil, Abe, 1948 Feb 2; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - to Manskleid, Felix, 1948 Feb 16; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Martin, Hugh, 1960 Jun 30; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Mayer, Harry (Editor of Women's Wear Daily), 1935 May 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Melnick, Linda & Danny, 1955 Apr 18; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Meltzer, Herman I., 1945 Mar 14; typed letter (incomplete) (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Meltzer, Herman I., 1945 Jul 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Mercer, Johnny, 1942 Feb 6; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - to Mercer, Johnny, 1942 Feb 9; carbon (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Mercer, Johnny, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - to Meredith, Burgess, 1952 Mar 13; telegram (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Meyer, Joe, 1941 Mar 13; carbon (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Minnelli, Vincente, 1933 Nov 7; telegram (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Mitchell, Loften, [1957-1958?]; authograph letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Mitchell, Loften, 1958 Apr 22; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - to Moss, Carlton, 1947 Apr 3; carbon (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Meyers, Henry, [?] Mar 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Meyers, Henry to Harburg, Eddy, [no date]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Myers, Henry, [1968]; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 185)
      - Nadal, Laura, 1953 Jan 29; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - to Nadal, Laura, 1953 Feb 12; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - Nathanson, Yale S., 1944 Jan 16; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - Nathanson, Yale S., 1944 Feb 22; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - Nathanson, Yale S., 1948 Jan 10; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - to Nathanson, Yale S., 1948 Jan 27; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - to Niel, Larry, 1952 Oct 31; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - Nixon, Virginia Morris, 1965 Mar 11; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 186)
      - O'Casey, Sean & Eileen, [1962 Dec 18]; autograph letter signed (postcard) (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - O'Casey, Sean, Eileen, Breon, Shwann, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Orgel, Lee, 1962 Sep 26; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Orgel, Lee, [1962?]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, Dixie [Mrs. William Bradley], [1966] Jan; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1947 Mar 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1948 Jan 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - to Otis, William Bradley, 1948 Feb 5; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1954 Feb 19; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1955 Mar 6; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1957 Dec 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1959 Mar 1; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - to Otis, William Bradley, 1960 Jan 5; typed letter signed, draft (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - to Otis, William Bradley, 1960 Jan 18; typed letter signed draft (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1960 Dec 30; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1962 Jan 19; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1965 Dec 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1966 Apr 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1966 Aug 23; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
        (Enclosure: prose piece, "The End," photocopy)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1967 Jan 29; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1967 Apr 15; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1967 Oct 25; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1967 Dec 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - Otis, William Bradley, 1968 May 22; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - to Otis, William Bradley, 1968 Jan 5; carbon, signed (Box 22, Folder 187)
      - [Patrick, John], [no date]; typed letter draft (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Paul, Betty, 1954 Nov 11; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - to Paul, Betty, 1954 Nov 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Pearlman, Moshe, 1966 May 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Perelman, S[id] J., 1937 May 19; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Perelman, S[id] J., 1942 Dec 16; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Perkiss, Ellen S., 1965 Mar 10; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Perry, Eleanor, [no date]; typed letter signed [initialed] (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Poitier, Sidney, 1967 Oct 10; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - to Polski, Perry W., 1954 Mar 15; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Popper, Martin, 1961 Jun 18; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Prince, Harold S. [re: offer to do lyrics for Fiorello], 1958 Jun 20; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - Quaney, Barbara [re: Channel 2 show], [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 188)
      - to Reilly, Frank C., 1945 Jan 24; carbon (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Robin, Leo, 1934 Jan 27; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Robinson, Earl, [1942-1944?]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Robinson, Earl, 1966 Apr 22; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Robinson, Earl, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Roden, Hattie, 1953 Mar 4; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Rodgers, Dick [Richard], 1956 Jul 4; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - to Rodgers, Dick, 1961 Nov 18; typed letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Rodgers, Dick, 1961 Nov 29; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1961 Apr 19; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Rose, Billy, 1944 Jan 13; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Rosen, John ("Fries"), 1961 Jun 19; autograph letter signed, note (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Rosen, Dr. Samuel, 1953 Jan 7; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Rosen, Dr. Samuel, 1966 Mar 15; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Ruby, Harry, 1962 Aug 5; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 189)
      - Saidy, Fred, [1967] May 27; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Schachter, Larry W., 1933 Aug 10; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Schary, Dore, 1944 May 18; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Schuler, Robert C., Munsel-Schuler Productions, Inc., 1968 Jun 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Schwartz, Arthur, [?] May 16; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Shannon, William, 1958 May 9; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Shapiro, Jonas J., 1937 Nov 22; telegram (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Shaw, Marian (Mrs. Irwin), 1967 Sep 30; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Shaw, Marian, 1967 Oct 16; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - [Sher?], Jack, 1959 May 18; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Sherover, Miles M., 1959 Dec 6; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Shubert, Lee, [no date]; telegram (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - to Smith, Oliver, 1945 Feb 28; typed letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Smolin, Nat (re: "A Blessing," poem by E.Y. Harburg published in N.Y. Post, 1940 Jun 13), 1940 Jun 17; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Snow, Edgar, 1950 Jul 24; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Snow, Edgar, 1966 Mar 2; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Stavis, Barrie, 1948 Jan 30; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - to Styne, Jule, [no date]; typed letter, draft (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Sunshine, Louis (M.D.), 1968 Aug 19; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - Suskind, David, [no date]; autograph letter signed (Box 22, Folder 190)
      - to Trumbo, Dalton, 1957 Apr 10; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - to Wachsman, Bob, 1952 Jan 14; carbon, photocopy (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - Wallace, Mike, 1962 Jun 28; typed letter signed (Box 22, Folder 191)
      - to Warner, Jack, 1941 Feb 14; carbon (Box 22, Folder 191)